EPISODE 32
Dad, Leshan has gone mad.
She has simply gone mad.
What a disgrace. What a disgrace!
This shrew is causing trouble again.
Let go of Zhuniang quickly.
If you hit her, I will return the favor.
I won't let you off this time.
Good and evil will eventually be repaid.
Do not rejoice if it arrives late.
But the time has not yet come.
You two,
if you can curb your old ways,
you might be able to cling to life.
If you continue to stir up trouble
and hurt innocent lives,
I will not tolerate this.
Punishing the wicked is exhausting.
Fainting.
- Quick.
- Sister.
- Quick. Didn't you see her fainting?
Quickly carry her back to the room.
Get up quickly, sister.
- Zhuniang, are you alright?
- Sister.
Help her up.
My lady.
Gently.
- Be careful.
- Here.
- Come.
- Son.
Come on.
Could she be possessed?
Mother, now is not the time
to ask questions.
Saving her is urgent.
Summon the physician.
Quick, go.
- Sir.
- What?
They're beating to kill.
What…
What on earth is going on here?
My lord,
a possessed person is no trivial matter.
When it strikes,
one doesn't even recognize family.
It strikes at anyone on sight.
With all her energy exhausted,
she momentarily fainted.
What will she be like
once she wakes up again?
That's still hard to say.
Should we tie her up first?
My lord, we called
- physician Wang for a consultation.
- No need.
Haven't we prepared
the demon-repelling blood?
Bring a bowl of it.
Yes.
I'm certainly not drinking that blood.
You're tricking me.
Aren't you possessed?
Where in this world
are there ghosts and evil spirits?
I'm afraid the most evil thing
is the human heart.
I thought
you were going
to beat up my parents as well.
I'm pretending
to be crazy to punish the evil.
But why beat the elderly without a reason?
My mother said
robbing the rich to help the poor,
that's called a knight-errant.
Bullying the weak, that's called a tyrant.
I'm defiant and fierce,
but also renowned and upright.
Your sister-in-law's hurt people.
Otherwise, why would I beat them?
Tonight is but a minor punishment
for a major admonition.
Once I seize ironclad evidence of murder,
I'll send it
to the Kaifeng Court for prosecution.
By then, you won't be able to stop it.
My second sister
is the most acerbic and narrow-minded.
Having been beaten, would she let you off?
Meet force with force. When water comes,
pile on dirt to keep it out.
There's nothing wrong,
yet you still cling to my bed.
What, you can't bear to leave?
You wish.
Just wait.
When my sister gets up tomorrow,
she'll definitely incite Mother
to teach you a lesson.
How dare she
openly beat her sister-in-law?
Causing such a commotion
and still have the face
to run back to her parents' house.
You go pull her down for me.
I'll give her a couple of slaps
to see if she dares to fight back.
Please calm your anger. It's taboo
to scold a daughter-in-law in public.
You don't want to be gossiped about,
or lose your dignity.
We can only persuade her
with kind words to turn back.
Once the family door is shut,
act as one pleases.
Not afraid that she'll fly
out of the palm of your hand.
You go.
Just say that I have a couple
of important words to entrust.
Ask her to come down nicely.
Her domineering spirit
is truly rare in the world.
We servants are likely unable
to dissuade her.
Timid as a mouse.
I will go myself.
I'd like to see her try to shirk.
- Li Leshan.
- Go.
Stop.
Where are we going?
Quick, call someone to chase!
I am your mother-in-law.
If you dare to act rashly, family rules
and moral norms won't spare you.
Mother-in-law, don't be afraid.
Although I'm from a humble family,
I know the hierarchical order.
I rashly schemed to have you come here.
I have my own reasons.
Once you arrive at the place
you will understand everything.
What kind of place is this?
So cramped and narrow.
The smell of horse urine
and cow dung is everywhere.
The carriage almost stalled.
What do you want me to see?
And we've been waiting so long.
It's here.
Indeed, one corpse and two lives.
The evidence is irrefutable.
They should take the corpse
to the court for confirmation.
Only then can they console
the soul of the daughter.
Imagine if it were commoners
without wealth or power, they wouldn't
dare to report to the officials.
This is quite strange, indeed.
The Zhang family, without wealth or power,
dare confront the Yangs for wrongdoing.
Leaving Yinping's corpse,
isn't it just the right way
to ask for more funeral expenses?
Why a midnight burial?
Unless she took someone else's money
and intentionally framed Yang…
my husband.
They also fear that the authorities will
investigate and the truth will be exposed.
That's why it was secret.
YANG MANSION
Slow down.
- Careful.
- Ah!
Li Leshan, you dare to come back.
We've searched all over Bianjing
and also inquired at Sifu House.
Where have you hidden my mother?
If you don't tell the truth,
don't blame me
for taking it to your Li family.
You are really muddled in your actions.
My mother is your mother-in-law.
A transgression
to a superior is an offense.
Upon investigation, no one
in your Li family can escape involvement.
Hurry up and explain.
It will also save us
from a major conflict.
Mother-in-law, please step out.
Mother.
Mother, you…
It's too stuffy inside the house.
I asked my daughter-in-law
to accompany me for a walk.
Don't make a fuss over it.
Disperse now.
Mother, I have been worried
about you all day.
Mother.
Li Leshan.
What kind of spell
did you cast on my mother?
My lord's injuries haven't healed.
I must return to attend to him.
I must take my leave first.
What exactly has Li Leshan done?
She's charmed Mother so much
her speech has changed.
I've really underestimated her.
This demoness.
She's brewed a potent enchantment potion.
Even Mother has been deceived by her.
- Quick, it's killing me.
- Come on.
Quickly help me back.
- It's Li Leshan's fault.
- Ouch.
Slow down.
My mother really believed your words?
Of course.
Seeing is believing. How could she not?
Ever since I came of age,
I've only seen her bickering
with the concubines every day.
Competing over prestige,
dignity, and sons,
as if there's nothing else worth doing.
I'm her underachieving son.
Can't bring her any honor.
Instead, I cause discord
between the parents.
Though she defends me verbally,
in her heart, resentment is inevitable.
And others add fuel
to the fire with their words,
as if all the evils
of the world are my doing.
That's because
of your unyielding and unruly nature.
Your actions give others
the opportunity to falsely accuse you.
But that's my own business.
No need for you to meddle.
I've arranged for men
to lie in ambush at the cemetery.
I've discussed it
with your mother already.
Should we capture Zhang's family
and hand them to the authorities
to charge them
with the crime of extortion?
Guess what your mother said?
I really don't want to know.
She said, "Tomorrow, deliver a generous
gift to the Zhang family to appease them.
Give Yinping a proper burial
and put the matter to rest."
Turning someone in to the authorities
would certainly be satisfying.
But it's inevitable
that others will still criticize you
for coercing a servant girl
and for driving her to her death.
Although your mother is misled,
she does truly care about you.
She's not doing it for me.
She's afraid of people saying
the Yangs abuse their power
and oppresses the common folk.
Li Leshan,
you've been pulling effort
and carefully planning for me.
You couldn't possibly
have changed your mind,
intending to stay
and become my wife, right?
What are you trying to do?
Leshan,
you've worked hard to exonerate Xian.
What do you want?
My mother often says since ancient times,
families who rise through meanness
never enjoy lasting wealth and honor.
When children and grandchildren
are rebellious,
they'll reap what they sowed.
Now that I'm married into the Yang family,
firstly, I want harmony
throughout the Yang family
and a legacy of integrity.
Secondly, I want my husband
to have a change of heart and start anew
to become a better person.
Changing his stubborn nature?
You're dreaming.
If he could change,
not to mention tolerating you a little,
I'd even set up an ancestral tablet
for you to ensure your long life
and willingly burn incense
three times a day for you.
Once in my hands,
let alone flesh and blood,
even the straight and strong poplars,
if I say bend, they will bend.
They will do whatever I say.
However,
I still have to ask you for something.
Without it, I can't deal with him.
What thing?
I want the power to lead the Yang family.
I want that Gold Master Seal
in your hands.
From today on,
without the gold seal in my hand,
even if you have
tens of thousands in wealth,
you won't be able to get a coin
from the accounting house.
Yet more ragged
than the beggars at the street corner.
Li Leshan, you've got quite the nerve.
What?
My lord.
Leave.
Can't order you around anymore? Get out.
Have someone else come in.
Why are you scolding him?
You're eating less, looking all gloomy.
And the bone injury
is taking so long to heal.
We rely on him for everything.
It's rash to replace him
with someone else.
Where can we find someone
as handy as him?
In that case, have the accountant
lift the ban, and I'll take my medicine.
- Just put it there.
- Yes.
My lord, time for your medicine.
- Just…
- Take the medicine.
It suits both of us.
Wait until I'm fully recovered,
- then we'll settle accounts.
- All right, all right.
Once your legs are better,
you'll feel the force
of my gold pod again.
I'd rather die than drink it.
- Drink or not?
- I won't drink.
My lord.
My lord, my lady,
the Li family has sent someone.
- Have them come in quickly.
- Yes.
- Madam, my wife is bullying--
- Shut up.
Cutting off the source of your
financial disaster is for your own good.
Madam.
You're driving me crazy.
Shut up, no talking.
You may not speak.
How come it's you?
It seems we have come
at an inconvenient time.
Mother knows the fifth brother-in-law
loves her candied meat buns.
She rendered the lard
in the third watch of the night.
These two baskets are freshly steamed,
fragrant and sweet.
She wanted to deliver them personally,
but really couldn't leave the shop.
She also insisted I bring some
winter melons and eggplants
from the Chai family homestead.
I said the Yang family is very wealthy.
There's nothing good they haven't seen.
She said those are fresh crops
from the field.
Even the palace
can't get such fresh produce.
By the way,
she let me check on you
to see if you are bullying
your husband again.
Yes, yes, yes.
No, no, no.
Just kidding.
It's nice Madam thinks of me,
and I have her on my mind too.
The crab roe buns
made by our chef taste extremely good.
It's famous in Bianjing.
I had him make several more boxes to share
with my mother-in-law and sisters.
A friend of mine will also bring some
fresh cherries and golden apricots.
If you don't mind,
stay here a couple more days
- and take them all back for me.
- No, that won't do.
Qiongnu,
the shop can't do without you
even for a moment.
But when coming here, Mom said
the Yang family
has a big and beautiful garden
filled with all sorts
of exotic flowers and plants.
She asked you to show me around properly.
There's no rush to go back.
What's there to admire in the garden?
It's because she's afraid I'll bully
Yang Xian, sending you to watch me.
Good that you are aware of it.
Still annoyed?
I have something serious to tell you.
Leave us.
Mom asked me to pass on a message.
It was his fault at the beginning.
No wonder you resent him.
But now that the bridal palanquin
has entered the Yang family's gate,
everyone acknowledges you two
as husband and wife.
Like nails hammered into stone,
it can never be changed again.
This incessant arguing,
is it pleasing to the eye or to the ear?
Don't give others something to talk about.
Did I snatch a bridal palanquin,
forcibly took someone's wife,
or act lawlessly?
Act upright, sit straight.
Being fair to the heavens.
I'm not afraid of being talked about.
Disobedient.
Beating the husband, scolding
the sisters-in-law, just name it.
Behind our backs, people curse Mother.
They will blame Mom
for not teaching her daughter well,
allowing a domineering daughter.
I'm begging you.
For the sake of our mother
and the reputation of the Li family,
be nicer to your husband.
When I see him, it reminds me of the
forced marriage and kidnapping incident.
I'm so angry I could hit him.
You may not be fond of him,
but he sure fancies you.
You hated him and got physical.
Did he fight back, for even a little?
If you don't believe me,
just try showing him some kindness once.
It would make him overjoyed.
Alright, alright.
Forget about it. The boring talks
make me impatient.
Don't you just love pearls?
I've just acquired a new pearl crown.
It was a gift from Lady Jieyu
from the palace.
I'll have someone bring it.
Let's both admire it.
You sure are stubborn.
Here, eat this.
Leshan.
So, your leg healed a while ago
and yet you dared
to sneak out for hunting.
It seems you've been
hiding some personal savings.
That doesn't give you the right
to plot against your husband.
I just checked the ledger yesterday.
You, Master Yang,
live a life of luxury and wealth.
All your expenses go to hosting banquets,
frolicking, and hunting.
You spend thousands of gold
in a single month.
Only to entertain a few worthless fellows.
Even dogs are more loyal
than those few scoundrels and cronies.
I saw through it long ago.
Yang Xian, you are no fool.
Indulging in pleasures,
you've given up on yourself.
In this family,
who actually cares about you?
You…
There is no one in the Yang family
that I care about.
Who am I supposed to impress?
Unless my lady takes pity
and agrees to be my true wife.
Someday, I will earn
a noble title for my lady.
And that would only be right.
I never expected that in my lord's heart,
I would hold such a position.
My lady is willing to help me
to this extent.
Such great kindness.
I should certainly return the favor.
At my lady's service.
If you want me to be your wife,
have you exchanged betrothal gifts
or set a wedding date?
The Yang family hasn't offered a bride
price nor completed any formalities.
You haven't offered incense
at the temple.
Without a proper name and declaration,
how do you claim to be married?
I have an imperial gold plaque,
a match made in heaven.
- You.
- Beat as you will.
Rascal.
Luckily, I was prepared in advance.
Even when Mr. Du
seeks to marry my eldest sister,
he must first pass the three challenges.
This is my family's tradition.
I'm afraid that even if
I pass 30 challenges,
someone will still turn their back on me.
You really want to ask
for my hand in marriage?
My third sister
once asked her husband to swear,
if the wife has a short life and the
couple is forever separated by death,
the husband must mourn for three years
before he may remarry.
I'm more overbearing than my sisters.
If I die first,
I'll take
my husband's possessions with me.
Even if it means burning them to ashes,
I will not share
a single penny with others.
If you are dead and buried in the evening,
I'll bury myself at midnight to follow.
Once a promise is made,
it's unbreakable as stone.
We'll clap hands as an oath
and never go back on our words.
Good. I swear by the moon,
if you truly can pass
the three challenges,
then I am willing to commit
my entire life to you.
If I break the promise
and the oath, punish me
to be abandoned by everyone,
as a lifelong widow.
I don't trust you unless
you sleep in my bed.
The couple sleeps on separate beds.
Mother will ask and the servants gossip.
It wouldn't be good if Mother-in-law
knows it.
Without passing the three challenges,
we are not husband and wife yet.
We'll live with borders, like Chu and Han.
Dare encroach the slightest bit,
and you shall be dead.
Go to sleep.
My lady.
My lady,
where are you going so late at night?
To admire the moon.
He is putting on an act everywhere,
seeking to win my pity.
I shouldn't agree
to these three challenges.
What if he…
Do I really have to marry him?
- Don't worry.
- You are of no use.
When will we finally
get rid of that calamity?
Who's there?
My lady.
My lady, slow down.
I'll just go get a lantern.
My lady, you walk too fast.
This…
I don't know who this shameless one is,
tarnishing my lady's discerning eyes.
Tomorrow, I'll report to the mistress.
The golden crow accompanies
the laurels of the moon.
The sun and the moon vie for radiance.
What great ambition and spirit.
This embroidery pattern is rare.
The needlework skill is also uncommon.
Don't act rashly and alert the enemy.
Keep it well.
Yes.
Things will eventually
sort themselves out.
What's there to worry about?
Set the exam questions
to be extremely difficult.
Let him know it's difficult and withdraw.
Lion dance?
Before the dragon boat race each year,
there's always a lion dance contest
for the top prize.
For the winner, the emperor
grant positions and bestows gold.
It's truly a splendid sight.
If you win first place,
then you've passed the first challenge.
Lion dance to grab the prize? It can't be.
It's true.
Your good brother
is recruiting capable people,
eager to win in the Lion King contest.
It must be that shrew instigating trouble.
Mom has become indifferent recently
and neglected everything.
I heard that shrew
took over Mom's Gold Master Seal
and wants to thoroughly check
the account books of these past years.
What if she discovers your doings
these few years?
What should we do?
Rest assured. The accounts I've done,
ordinary people can't spot anything amiss.
Let alone every Dragon Boat Festival,
Jinming Pool attracts experts.
Dangers lurk everywhere.
Picking the top prize isn't easy.
Even if a few people die,
it's not surprising.
No way. After all, he is my own brother.
Even if I dislike him,
I'll just find a way to drive him out.
Taking lives over money matters
is unacceptable.
Where is your mind going?
It's just to teach him a lesson or two
to dispel your resentment.
Make them obedient in the future.
Also let the couple
learn their lessons.
It's not yet their turn
to be in charge of the Yang family.
Good plan.
Also, a good way to deal with that shrew.
Intimidate and subdue her.
My good wife.
You're really smart.
Stand firm.
Be careful.
My lord, be careful.
That prize is hung high. It's nothing like
the lion dance on the ground.
Make sure you stay stable.
If one falls from a high place,
at least it will cause fractures.
At worst, it could be life-threatening.
Be extremely careful.
When my grandfather was alive,
I performed a lion dance for his birthday.
I must lack practice.
- Again.
- Come on.
Brother Yang.
I've just returned
and I hear you're risking your life here.
Don't make everyone worried.
They say that Li Leshan is fierce
like a tiger and cruel like a wolf.
Cold-hearted and malicious,
a match for a demon.
What has bewitched your senses?
Not to mention
she plays you around every day.
You still treat her like a treasure.
For such a violent woman,
it's not worth risking your life.
- Let's continue.
- Okay.
She is probably fooling you around
and will not truly keep her word.
When the Dragon Boat Festival comes,
all the people in Bianjing
will come to watch the contest.
Surrounded by such a crowd,
if you really lose,
it will be a great embarrassment.
Yang, slow down.
Aren't you afraid of heights?
Dare slander Leshan again,
I'll crush your tongue.
- Continue.
- Slow down.
Qiansheng,
why don't you try to persuade him?
Enough said.
He's gone mad, truly mad.
Slow down.
Be careful.
Sort out this mugwort carefully.
My lady.
It's almost dusk.
Your husband has not returned home yet.
Yes.
Why are you looking at me?
My lady.
The Lord is in fear of heights
from childhood.
I'm afraid he is not suited
for the contest.
- Take it to him.
- Yes.
These are the corn dumplings
my mother made.
Do not mention me in this.
Nor are you allowed to look at me.
Try the perilla drink I brewed at home.
Sir, please have a taste.
Fresh pastries on sale.
My lady, the iced beverage I've brewed.
Would you like to try?
They're all very tasty.
- Come and have a taste.
- Don't be in a hurry.
- Come, come.
- Why is it built so high?
Too overconfident.
Absolutely not.
What is this?
He is just a porcelain vase.
- Just for show.
- Exactly.
How could he possibly win?
Look at my foolish brother.
Always causing trouble
on normal days.
There are no outsiders here today.
There's nothing that can't be said.
I have no idea
who incited him,
making a fuss about
joining the Lion King Festival.
And he's making a big show of it,
making it known
to everyone with his clamor.
Over these years,
those who have won the prize
are all brave warriors.
It's not his turn at all.
Just look.
They've all come to witness
the joke of our Yang family.
No wonder Father hasn't come.
It would embarrass me to death.
Can't believe they're a family.
When the brother is in the arena,
they don't cheer for him,
but they discourage and mock.
Is she really his sister?
Poor man.
Look, someone from the palace
has come too.
GENEROUS AND KIND
Yesterday, Uncle specially
visited my second cousin,
earnestly advising him not to go.
Turns out it's because
His Majesty came in person.
Alright, now, we will
embarrass ourselves
in front of the royal family.
My presumptuous dear brother.
If this turns out to be a complete defeat,
on the face of Jieyu,
there will be no glory.
That's enough.
Nobody is allowed
to speak dishearteningly.
What's the matter with you?
It's no good.
- What's happened?
- I have a stomachache.
Stomachache.
Such a critical moment.
How did you end up with a bad stomach?
Right, if you leave, what do we do?
Even if it's the last thing you do,
you have to hold on for me.
Otherwise, at this time, where will I find
a drummer in such a hurry?
The lion dance contest needs a drummer.
The momentum can't be weak.
Yeah, if you leave, who will cheer for us?
Can't do it.
It's not going to work.
What can we do about this?
This…
What should we do?
It's already this late.
Where are you going?
Xian.
Follow me.
Xian, that pole is high.
It makes my heart tremble.
You can't go.
Go and see what's going on.
What? Let me do it?
What's wrong?
You wield your staff with divine skill.
Are you scared to switch to drumsticks?
Why wouldn't I dare?
It's just that…
Showing off in front of a big crowd,
it's not proper for a lady.
The Yang family
will have trouble with you again.
Xian, not just anyone
can replace the drummer.
Stop causing a scene
and being a laughingstock.
Let's go.
I don't need a drummer.
I just want you to watch me win.
Li Leshan, you are
a woman of valor, a true heroine.
I love your candid and bold character,
unrestrained and unbridled.
Go if you want. Why fear others' gossip?
Leshan.
- Leshan.
- Mother.
Just let him.
Mother, how did you come here?
I asked Fuhui to attend the business.
My son-in-law is competing.
How could I not come to cheer him on?
Leshan.
In Bianjing, women who are at the helm
and start business are no less.
We are not afraid of their mockery.
Besides, your husband has let you go.
Why fear what others might say?
Everyone, compete well for me.
Today, if anyone put on a pitiful face,
I will knock them out.
Good.
Mother.
This time, our Li family will make
a great name for ourselves in Bianjing.
Just right.
Let all Bianjing see the fine demeanor
of the Li family's daughter.
Put those men to shame.
Good.
Well…
Qiongnu, let's go.
- Why is there a lady playing the drum?
- Exactly.
That's my daughter.
Leshan.
How come your Yang family
also has ladies entering the arena?
Oh brother.
How dare you act recklessly
in the imperial presence?
Truly formidable.
Yang Xian.
He is back.
Good.
Bravo.
Keep it up.
My lord, hurry.
Go on. Go on.
My lord.
Is everything ready?
It's been ready for a while.
Don't blame me for being heartless.
Why not just accept your fate
and spend a lifetime
as a good-for-nothing?
My lord, be careful.
Charge.
Just a little bit more.
Yang Xian.
Be careful.
So close.
Got it.
I won.
Wonderful.
It's my son-in-law.
My son-in-law is so formidable.
Nice.
Good.
Leshan, I won!
Well done.
Truly good.
Bravo.
I'm coming.
My lord, slow down.
- Slow down, my lord. Are you alright?
- Yang Xian.
How is it?
- I'm fine.
- This is murder.
They've committed murder.
- Arrest them.
- Are you alright?
Dare to harm my son-in-law.
It's him.
- What are you doing?
- Catch him.
- It's him.
- Let me go.
- It was you. I saw it.
- Who saw it?
Who saw it?
Clearly, it was your son-in-law.
He kicked me down.
Yes, it was him
who caused us to lose the target.
You pay.
I'll hit you.
Hit you.
The shrew is hitting people.
Take this.
Which family's fierce lady are you,
playing tough?
Others want to seize the mark.
But they are bent on taking your life.
Just now, from below,
I saw a flash of silver on his shoe.
Something's fishy.
Take him down.
You wronged me.
- The Yang family is bullying others.
- Take it easy.
Take it slow.
Please hear me out.
Let go first.
Xian.
His Majesty graces
the grand event at Jinming Pool.
This fighting and brawling of yours
is a serious crime.
Dishonoring the court adds to the offense.
While His Majesty
has not yet passed sentence,
I hope you will think thrice
before acting.
Do not make it difficult for Jieyu.
It is precisely because it's in front
of His Majesty, under the bright heavens,
that we must expose
those evil spirits in their true form.
Quick, pull off his boots.
Let go of me.
Look.
Everyone, look.
Indeed, a sharp blade is hidden.
This is attempted murder. Look.
What?
Hold him down.
All evidence says you're guilty.
You still run.
By His Majesty's words,
summon the Yang couple for questioning.
Yes.
What did I say?
This is His Majesty deciding your crime.
It's better to keep the peace
and appease people.
Alright, disperse now.
You are all young lords
with impetuous energy.
That's why there was an uproar.
Both sides are at fault.
The fault does not lie with one alone.
My brother is always rash.
I apologize for him.
I apologize on his behalf to everyone.
Let's downplay the issue
and value harmony.
How dare you…
defend the murderer? Isn't that equivalent
to being an accomplice?
I'm going to see His Majesty.
I'll settle the score with you
once I return.
My lady, let's go.
Come on.
You foolish thing.
All my good intentions are wasted.
You don't know what's good for you.
You don't stand up for your family,
you argue in defense of the assailant.
Fortunately, it was in public.
You still wish to
muddle truth with falsehood.
- You…
- What are you saying?
You're like a monkey showing off your
climbing skills, unaware of your flaws.
Let's see if he turns red or not.
I see it.
Making a fool of himself.
- Blushing furiously.
- No laughing allowed.
Stop laughing.
What are you laughing at?
You.
Harmony is precious.
Subtitle translation by: Zhong Wenlong